polishforums.com 2006-12-13

# Privacy Policy, Contact Details, and Code of Conduct

Updated on: October 18, 2006

[Polish Forums dot com](http://www.polishforums.com/) (known as PolishForums.com, PolishForum.com, and PolandForums.com) is owned and operated by Polonia, LLC. Forum moderators are volunteers based in the US and Poland; they have been carefully selected by the owners to help enforce the site's acceptable rules and guidelines.

**I. Quick, Simple, and Trustworthy**

Polish Forums respect your privacy. All information you provide us with is completely confidential. We will not resell, or trade your personal information with any other parties. That includes your name, email address, private posts, or any other personal details. 

We do not collect any non-personal identification information nor we do not collect any personally identifiable offline contact information.

We will not use any outside company to display targeted advertisements based on your personal information. From time to time (up to two times a year) we may contact selected members by email to inform them about the status of their membership and offer new services.

Admin and all moderators of Polish Forums who have access to your personal information are required to keep the information strictly confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to ensure that the Polish Forums website meets the highest standards and follows social norms.

**II. Security**

PolishForums.com has adequate security measures to protect against misuse, alteration, and loss of your personal information or forum messages. In order to make sure that other posters do not use your name or nick name in their posts, you are strongly encouraged to [sign up for a free account](http://www.polishforums.com/index.php?action=registernew). Members can also edit their preferences and subscribe to any topic; this allows them to receive other posters' replies to their personal email account.

**III. Forum Code of Conduct**

1\. Using derogatory words is strictly prohibited.

2\. Posters should avoid political and religious subjects. Admin and moderators have the right to delete or edit posts that relate to political or religious aspects or may lead to political or religious discussions.

3\. It is possible for Admin and moderators to determine which username/s the poster has used when submitting a message as _Username [Guest]_. It is strongly recommended that one person uses only one username when posting to our forums.

4\. Intentional posting of the same or very similar message by the same user more than once will be treated as spam and deleted.

**IV. Deleting and Editing Forum Posts**

Only Admin and assigned moderators have the ability to delete or edit posts that deem to be inappropriate. A member can edit his/her post within 24 hours after making the post, but he or she cannot delete it completely. If you are a signed-up member and want to delete your post, you may email us at info@PolishForums.com. Be sure to include your email address and link to the message. Be advised that such requests may take up to seven business days to become effective and not all requests will be fulfilled. 

**V. Deleting Forum Members**

Polish Forums administrator and moderators have the right to ban or remove without warning a guest poster or member who has breached group ettiquette and/or has posted a message that does not meet social norms. You may contact info@PolishForums.com if you cannot post or have problems with accessing the forums.

**VI. Becoming a Contributing Writer**

If you have knowledge about Poland and Polish society and would like to become a contributing writer, please email us at info@PolishForums.com. Upon approval, your articles will be published on our website. Depending on our agreement, you may be reimbursed for your time.

**VII. Policy Changes**

All our Privacy Policy changes will be posted on this web page at least seven days before any major changes are to take place. 

**VIII. Contacting PolishForums.com**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement or if you need to contact us, please use the following information:

PolishForums.com  
PO Box 101  
Mount Prospect, IL 60056  
USA  
Email: info@PolishForums.com 

Copyright (C) 2006 PolishForums.com
